psychologicallyunemployable.net 2015-10-24

# Privacy Policy - Psychologically Unemployable

**Privacy Policy**

**  
INTRODUCTION**  
Your privacy is essential to us. Here in http://psychologicallyunemployable.net/, we believe that privacy is a top priority. We know that you care how information about you is used and shared. Thus, we provide this Privacy Policy to summarize our procedures and practices as regards to information collection and use. This will serve you as a guide in making an intelligent decision in sharing your information with us. By visiting http://psychologicallyunemployable.net/, you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy and hereby accept the procedures and practices stated in this herein.

**COVERAGE**  
This Privacy Policy also outlines our privacy practices on our corporate website. This would describe and explain how we take care and handle your personal information. You agree to this Privacy Policy, in its entirety, when you: (1) access or use the Website; and/or (2) apply for the publisher (“Publisher”) and/or advertiser (“Advertiser” and together with the Publishers, “Clients”) services available through the Website (“Services”). If you do not agree with the terms and conditions of our Privacy Policy, please do not use or access the Website or apply for the Services.

**INFORMATION COLLECTION**  
If you attempt to become a Client or otherwise choose to provide information to us, this website shall collect Personal Information from you. This information includes, but is not limited to: name, address, telephone number, mobile number and/or email address. Once collected, we will store your information for a reasonable period of time for record keeping purposes. The information that we store is sometimes deleted as space requires or in the normal course of business.

**REMOVAL OF YOUR INFORMATION/OPTING OUT**

At anytime you want to opt out/unsubscribe you can click the link at the bottom of any of the emails and you will be removed from our database. You may also [contact us directly](http://psychologicallyunemployable.net/contact-me/ "Contact Me") and send an email and we will remove you immediately. This will take you out of our database, but if you optin to any websites linked from our site(third party sites) you should refer to their policies to opt out of their database list.

**  
DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION**  
Information that we collected and stored shall not be sold or make it for rent to or with others. Your personal information is not shared with any third parties, except:  
(a) where necessary to conduct business, such as invoicing Clients in connection with the Services or making payments to, or collecting money from, a Client;  
(b) in case of a breach of any agreement between Client and http://psychologicallyunemployable.net/;  
(c) when required by law, or requested by a court of competent jurisdiction;  
(d) in the event of http://psychologicallyunemployable.net/ bankruptcy, or if http://psychologicallyunemployable.net/ is sold or acquired; or  
(e) where http://psychologicallyunemployable.net/ determines, in its sole discretion, that such disclosure is necessary to protect the rights of http://psychologicallyunemployable.net/ and/or a third party, or necessary to protect http://psychologicallyunemployable.net/ from liability of any kind.  
In an effort to respect your privacy and our ability to keep the community free from bad actors, we will not otherwise disclose your personal information to law enforcement, other government officials, or other third parties without a subpoena, court order or substantially similar legal procedure, except when we believe in good faith that the disclosure of information is necessary to prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss or to report suspected illegal activity.

**COOKIES AND WEB BEACONS**  
We use “cookies” and web beacons to help us manage our Website. Cookies are small text files that contain a string of alphanumeric characters. Web beacons (also known as “1X1 pixels” or “clear GIFs”) are small strings of code that provide a method for delivering a graphic image on a web page or in an email message for the purpose of transferring data. Web users have the option of blocking the use of cookies by changing a setting in their browser. Web users can check their browser supplier’s website for details on how to do this.

**SECURITY**  
All collected information is stored in a technically and physically secure environment. While we use SSL encryption to protect Sensitive Information online, we also do everything in our power to protect PII (including Sensitive Information) off-line. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect our end-users’ personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.  
Once we receive the transmission of your personal information, we make reasonable efforts to ensure its security on our systems. Access to this information is strictly limited, and not accessible to the public. All our end-users’ personal information is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example a customer service representative) are granted access to the same.

**ACCESSING AND UPDATING PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
When you use our services, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your personal information and either to correct this data if it is inaccurate or to delete such data at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. We ask individual users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical, or for which access is not otherwise required. In any case where we provide information access and correction, we perform this service free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort. Some of our services have different procedures to access, correct or delete users’ personal information. We do retain personal information from closed accounts to comply with law, prevent fraud, collect any fees owed, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our policies and take other actions otherwise permitted by law.

**THIRD PARTIES**  
It should be stressed here that the websites of our advertiser and publisher clients as well as the websites on which we place advertisements or any third party websites linked to one of our sites also may collect information from you for various purposes, including, but not limited to providing advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. Such information may include non-personally identifiable information through the use of Cookies and other technology and any personally identifiable information you may choose to give in registering and transacting with such website. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. Although we choose our business partners and clients carefully, we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such third parties. You should check the applicable privacy policies of such third parties to determine how they handle any information they collect from you. If you disclose your information to others, whether they are bidders, buyers or sellers on our sites or other sites throughout the internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others.

**MINORS**  
This Website is not intended for visitors that are minors or under eighteen (18) years of age. http://psychologicallyunemployable.net/ does not knowingly solicit or collect information from individuals under the age of eighteen (18). If we determine that we have inadvertently collected personal information from someone under eighteen (18) years of age, we will take reasonable steps to purge this information from our database. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate and monitor the Internet activities of their children.

**CHANGES AND AMENDMENTS & NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES**  
http://psychologicallyunemployable.net/ reserves the right to change or update this Privacy Policy at any time by posting a clear and conspicuous notice on the Website explaining that we are changing our Privacy Policy. All Privacy Policy changes will take effect immediately upon their posting on the Website. Please check the Website periodically for any changes. Your continued use of the Website and/or acceptance of our e-mail communications following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of any and all changes.
